And
Speaker 1: Carrie Lake joins us now to talk about this. What a moment to see that federal charge against one of the worst out there. I think
like a
Speaker 2: lot of Americans, I was starting to think, well, maybe it won't happen, even though I've heard the news about, you know, all of the problems
Speaker 3: with her mortgage documents. I mean, that's real basic stuff. She's a top law enforcement officer. She should be thrilled that this administration is following the law,
Speaker 2: the letter of the law -
Right.
Speaker 2: tea. And the good news is I actually think that Tish is going to look really good in orange. I think
it might be
Speaker 2: her color.
Speaker 4: Hey, nobody's above the law, Carrie, as we learned so many times from
Speaker 1: Tish James. They're calling this retribution. And sure, why not? Let's call it retribution. But there has to be this for what they did. And that's the point. You remember how much time...
Speaker 1: Trump spent sitting in court, how hard they tried to humiliate him. And again, he goes 78 years. He never has any legal trouble. And all of a sudden he has 91 felonies at 79 years old. And you're telling me that's not political. This is necessary. The people that did this, this needs to happen to them. Otherwise, they'll just do it again. If a lesson isn't learned here, then these people will just get worse and they'll do it again.
Well, I
Speaker 5: don't think it's retribution at all. I think it is law and order. It's justice. There was a wrongdoing
Speaker 3: here. It sounds like it's a solid case. We're going to get more information as the days unfold. And I think it's going to be an open and shut case, a real easy one. It's all there in the documents and nobody forced anybody to sign a document. And so when you fill out these documents, it's really hard to prove otherwise that you are innocent when in fact...
Speaker 3: The evidence is right there in front of you, you know, and we think of what happened to President Trump and the fact that he was dragged through all of this nonsense. Meanwhile, New York City devolved into just a crime haven where criminals were running the streets, killing people, maiming people, hurting people and not being prosecuted. Maybe the good news is that when Tish does go to prison, there's going to be no criminals there because she didn't help lock any of them up.
But
Speaker 3: I know that we are going to start locking people up who are doing wrongdoing in places like New York, in places like Chicago, L.A., and other crime-ridden cities. And it's about time that we have law and order and that the people who pay their taxes work hard, can walk on the streets and not have to be surrounded by criminals, including potentially someone like Tish.
It
Speaker 1: really is just a reminder of just how dirty it is.
Speaker 1: The inner workings of these
Speaker 6 (lower-pitched voice): big blue cities are I mean how corrupt the people that get in I mean people like I mean How in the hell is tish james the attorney general of new york? How did that even happen and you see it when I mean it's the same reason we're about to have
Speaker 1: mamdani is as the mayor of this city It's it's just the republicans don't vote the democrats know they have it So you get the worst of the democrat party the primary is the election and you end up with these horrific people that are running the most important city in the world and
Speaker 3: Well, this is why we need to another thing that President Trump talks about, get back to real honest elections where we vote on Election
Speaker 2: Day. We don't have election month. We don't have mail in ballots because I think a lot of common sense voters have just given up in some of these blue states and blue cities. They say, why should I even vote? It's just rigged. It's just a mess. There's no chance. And so I hope we get
Speaker 3: to that point, because I think when we do have really true elections, one legal vote per legal voter, we don't end up with the tissues of the world. We don't end up with the Memdami's. We don't end up with the Gavin Newsom's. We end up with common sense people in office. And I think that's what we're going to start seeing. That's well said.
Speaker 7: I pray. Yeah. Same here. Carrie Lee, good to see you. Thanks so much.